(Raj:)My name is Little
Orphan Annie.
(Howard:)You killed my father.
(Howard:)Prepare to die.
(with accent):
My name is Darth Vader.
I am your father. Ah!
(Sheldon:)This is fun.
Good.
(Leonard:)It's nice
to see your mind off Amy.
(Barry:)What's going on with Amy?
(Sheldon:)Not that it's any
of your business,
(Sheldon:)but she broke up with me.
(Penny:)Really?
(Barry:)Good to know.
"Good to know"?
(Sheldon:)What's that supposed to mean?
Oh.
(Leonard:)I hate to say it, but it sounds
like he's interested in her.
(Sheldon:)Well, that's unacceptable.
(Leonard:)Oh, buddy, I get
that you don't like it,
(Leonard:)but it's not
really up to you.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, but he's dumb,
and his face is dumb.
(Leonard:)Look, even if it's not him,
(Leonard:)Amy's probably going
to date someone at some point.
(Sheldon:)You really think so?
(Leonard:)Of course.
She deserves to be happy.